//Questions and Options array

const quizArray = [
    {
        id: "0",
        question: "These are fundamental forces in quantum physics except",
        options: ["Superposition", "Electromagnetic force", "Entanglement", "Quantum"],
        correct: "Electromagnetic force",
    },
    {
        id: "1",
        question: "Heisenberg's uncertainty principle states that for a Quantum particle, we are not allowed to know the location and?",
        options: ["Momentum", "Time", "Space time", "Inertia"],
        correct: "Momentum",
    },
    {
        id: "2",
        question: "When quantum particle is observed, the following happens",
        options: ["It collapses the probability wave function", "It is suspended in spacetime", "It becomes quantum entangled", "Its trajectory speed is doubled"],
        correct: "It collapses the probability wave function",
    },
    {
        id: "3",
        question: "If two particles are quantum entangled, they share which of the following characteristics?",
        options: ["Trajectory", "Spacetime", "Magnetic force", "Non-locality"],
        correct: "Non-locality",
    },
    {
        id: "4",
        question: "In the Delayed Choice Quantum Eraser experiment, what is the function of the beam-splitter?",
        options: ["To obfuscate the path of the particle", "To split the entangled particles", "To speed up the photon", "To send the photon forward"],
        correct: "To obfuscate the path of the particle",
    },
    {
        id: "5",
        question: "The magnitude of the spin of a quantum particle is always _________",
        options: ["The square of the complex amplitude", "Velocity x direction", "One", "Gravity x direction"],
        correct: "One",
    }, {
        id: "6",
        question: "A qubit is a quantum bit of data. It can be put in superposition, what does this mean?",
        options: ["It can count as a double 0 or a double 1", "It can be a 0, a 1, or a combination of both", "It can be 0,1 or 2", "It must always be a 0 or a 1 to be able to read easier"],
        correct: "It can be a 0, a 1, or a combination of both",
    },
    {
        id: "7",
        question: "What's going on in this quantum circuit? <br> q [0] |0>-----H------------------ <br> q [1] |0>---------------------------",
        options: ["The first qubit is being deleted", "The first qubit is being entangled", "The first qubit is being added to", "The first qubit is being put into superposition"],
        correct: "The first qubit is being put into superposition",
    },
    {
        id: "8",
        question: "Which of the following is a near-term possibility of quantum computing?",
        options: ["Breaking encryption using Shor's algorithm", "Building video games using quantum computers", "Modeling extremely large molecules like DNA", "Discovering new types of computers"],
        correct: "Modeling extremely large molecules like DNA",
    },
    {
        id: "9",
        question: "How do you interact with qubits?",
        options: ["By placing the qubits in superposition", "By placing a gate on the circuit", "By placing the qubits in a 1, and a 0 arrangement", " By adding gates in the qubits"],
        correct: "By placing a gate on the circuit",
    },
];